This video is the shocka Seat I don't know which
Este vídeo es el shocka Seat no sé cuál
Rubius burger It's good, it has
hamburguesa de Rubius Está bueno tiene
3.1 million views and it has paid me
3,1 millones de views y me ha pagado
3.1000 3100 has paid me okay This video
3,1000 3100 me ha pagado vale Este vídeo
and it continues to generate me has generated
y me sigue generando me ha generado
40,000 subscribers 1000 views has
40,000 suscriptores 1000 views me ha
given me 1 2.7 2700 for 2.7 million
dado 1 2,7 2700 por 2,7 millones de
views so it's very similar Is there any that has
views o sea es muy parecido Hay alguno
a better cpm 5000 bucks It's that
Que tenga un cpm mejor 5000 pavos Es que
my CP has improved a lot and Uh it has
mi CP me ha mejorado bastante y Eh me ha
given me 5000 bucks for every million views They will
dado 5000 pavos por cada millón de views
give me instead of 1000 bucks 2000 more or
Me darán en vez de 1000 pavos 2000 más o
less I was talking a little about the cpm and
menos Estuve hablando un poco del cpm y
comparing the cpm that he has that has
comparando el cpm que él tiene que ha
improved I think that the cpm is not that it has
mejorado Yo creo que el cpm no es que le
improved but that YouTube has now
haya mejorado sino que YouTube ahora ha
improved the monetization in fact they play
mejorado la monetización de hecho saltan
more ads they have more control
más anuncios tienen más control en
against the appblock that you want that
contra del appblock que eso quieras que
are not things that add up a lot and well
no son cosas que suman bastante y bueno
Well basically he was showing a
Pues básicamente estuvo enseñando un
little bit of the quality of his channel in
poco la calidad de su canal en
monetization  And how much does it generate for some
monetización Y cuánto genera por algunos
videos, reaching more than 5000
vídeos llegando a generar más de 5000
for some videos, eh, look what
por algunos vídeos eh mira lo que gano
I earn a day from YouTube from the main channel:
yo al día de YouTube del Canal principal
250 bucks, 700 bucks, 600 bucks, 300 bucks,
250 pavos 700 pavos 600 pavos 300 pavos
300 bucks, 280 bucks
300 pavos 280 pavos